NUR FATIN LIYANA BINTI MD SOBHI

B-1-4, Danau Murni Condominium, Jalan 1/109F, Taman Danau Desa, 58100 Kuala Lumpur | +60 17 7070 134 | <u>liyanasobhi@gmail.com</u>



CAREER OBJECTIVE

A fresh graduate seeking for a career opportunity with a dynamic company. Possesses over two years of accumulated experience in food and beverages, admin, and customer service. Diligent, self-driven and a team player. Able to start work immediately.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Business Administration (Hons.), University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur. *Sep 2013 – Oct 2017* CGPA: 3.27/4.00.

Matriculation Accounting Program, Johore Matriculation College, Tangkak, Johor. *May* 2012 – *Apr* 2013

CGPA: 4.00/4.00. MUET: Band 4.

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM), Sekolah Tinggi Kluang, Kluang, Johor.

Jan 2010 – Dec 2011

8A's. (English: A+, Bahasa Melayu: A+, Maths: A)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Caffe Bene Malaysia, Mid Valley Megamall, Kuala Lumpur.

Barista

• Prepared food and beverages, and provided excellent customer service. Involved in the opening and/or closing of outlet. Involved in training new baristas when required. Monitored and maintained daily operations as per standard operating procedure.

AIA Bhd., Menara AIA, Jalan Ampang, Kuala Lumpur.

Sep 2016 – Feb 2017

Sep 2017 – present

Intern/Insurance Claims Assessor (Personal Accidents Operations-Claims)

• Processed insurance claims in compliance with regulatory guidelines (in POLA and MCS). Completed clerical tasks such as preparing letters and presentation slides, and data entry. Worked closely with managers regarding insurance claims and customer service. Organized departmental events from time to time (i.e.: team-building, gatherings).

Super Yin Nogori Sembilan Food Specialist

Feb 2016 - Sep 2016

Social Media Content Creator (Part-time)

• Created creative contents using Adobe Photoshop and online editing applications. Maintained engagement with customers on social media.

Boost Juice Bars, Pantai Hospital KL, Bangsar.

 $Jul\ 2015 - Feb\ 2016$

Team Leader (Part-time)

• Prepared food and beverages, provided excellent customer service. Involved in the opening and/or closing of outlet on a daily basis. Promoted to team leader within 3 months. Monitored and maintained daily operations as per standard operating procedure.

Koperasi Angkatan Tentera Malaysia Berhad, Kluang, Johor. *Clerk (contract).*

Dec 2012 – *Mar* 2013

• **Provided front-desk customer service. Involved in clerical tasks** such as cheque printing, data entry and letter preparation. **Engaged in simple bookkeeping** and filing activities

SKILLS

Language: Fluent in English and Bahasa Melayu.

Editorial/technical: Proficient in MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint). Possess basic skills in Adobe Photoshop. APA proficient.

Interpersonal: Possess excellent communication skills. Hardworking, organized, and pay attention to details. Able to take up a leadership role when required. Flexible when working with people of different backgrounds.

EXTRACURRICULAR INVOLVEMENT

3E Trip to Shanghai, China. (Faculty of Business and Accountancy).

16 – 21 July 2016

Logistics Department

- A one-week educational, exploratory, and experiential trip to Shanghai and Hangzhou, People's Republic of China. A joint-effort between Genting Malaysia Berhad and the Faculty of Business and Accountancy to allow students to experience cultural exchange and overcome challenges in a foreign country.
- Involved in research for accommodation and transportation.
- Ensured a smooth travel experience for participants.

Career Path 2015. (University of Malaya Business Club).

25 – 26 Mar 2015

Emcee.

- A two-day career fair targeted to students and alumni.
- Hosted the event and ensured a smooth event flow as per itinerary.

O-week 2014/2015 (University of Malaya Business Club).

12 – 13 Sep 2014

Head of Facilitators

- A two-day orientation program to welcome freshmen into the faculty.
- Directed, assisted, and monitored fellow facilitators to comply with their job scopes.

Futsal Team (Za'ba Residential College).

Sep 2013 – Sep 2015

Team member, goalkeeper.

• Participated in games and won awards in several occasions.

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

S.A.F.E.R Business Success Masterclass

May 2017

ADLA Group Sdn. Bhd.

Google AdWords Certification.

Jun 2016

Google Ignite Malaysia 2016

Public Service Department Scholarship Award.

Sep 2013

Local Bachelor Degree Program

Level 2 Certificate in Bookkeeping and Accounts.

Dec 2011

London Chamber of Commerce and Industry

REFERENCES will be provided upon request.